♪ BGM
We will now open the press conference commemorating the release of Equal Love 40th single Natsu Matopé.
Now, let's have the members take the stage. Please go ahead!
BGM
The lyrics of our 14th single "Natsu Matopee" are a coined word that combines the words "summer" and "onomatopee".
The lyrics use many onomatopoeic words to describe summer, such as gira gira, kin kin, and so on.
So now we would like to ask all the members to present the onomatopoeia that describes Ikolove.
I would like to ask each member to present an onomatopoeia that describes Ikolab.
Let's start with Hana Ohba, who will present the onomatopoeia.
Okay, Ms. Ooba, please.
Here is my iconomatopoeia.
It's "jan jan bakubaku".
Bakubaku? What does this mean?
When we were rehearsing for Iconoi Joy...
Mr. Sasahara gave me a gift of muscats from one of his employees.
He sent us three groups of muscats, Equilab, Noi Minia Joy, and Bakubaku.
Ikolove was the first to eat all the employee muscats!
By the way, who was the first?
I wonder.
They all said, "Open it. They were like, "What? It was like...
We were all blaming each other a little.
We all went to eat at once.
Thank you very much.
Now let's have Risa Otoshima present the iconomatopoeia.
Otoshima-san, please.Otoshima-san, please.
My iconography is "flap flap.
What do you mean by "flap flap"?
I mean before a concert or before an engine.
It's when people stay in the dressing room and don't get ready until right before the show.
So I chose "flapjacks" because it's not always easy to get ready for a show.
By the way, who is the slowest in preparation?
I'm sorry to say this, but...
Me and Saito Kihara, who is off today, are the slowest.
We always have a race to see who can get out first.
Which one of you has been faster recently?
I think I've been a little faster lately.
Then I'll be careful not to be too busy from now on.
Next, let's hear from Emily Otani who will give us her ikomatopee presentation.
Ms. Otani, please.
Goo goo goo!
Goo goo goo.
What does this mean?
Yes, during the interview
It's coming from someone's stomach.
Do you hear a lot of stomach rumblings?
Yes, it's quite a scene during the interview.
They are talking one by one.
What's that? It happens quite often.
Do you notice each other's stomach rumblings?When your stomach is growling, do you notice who's growling with each other?
A glimpse.
With a sideways glance.
Mayuka's tummy rumbled just now.
In the waiting room, my stomach rumbled quite loudly.
Oh no! I thought.
I hope it doesn't growl now.
Please eat something delicious after the show!
Now, let's hear Anna Yamamoto's gastric tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy tummy
Ms. Yamamoto, please.
Yes, my stomach is shaggy.
I think it's not good for an idol.
I think it's because many of the members of Equal Love have early morning lessons.
I have lessons early in the morning.
I think she's a bit sleepy.
I think they might be a little sleepy.
But there are not one or two members who seem to have a sleeping habit.
It's not just one or two.
More than half, almost half of the members
more than half of them come in with their hair uncut.
But recently I've been taking lessons at Ikonoijoy, so there are a lot of junior members.
I have a lot of junior members.
They have ribbons on their heads.
They look so cute.
But as far as I'm concerned, Equal Love has beenBut as far as I'm concerned, Equal Love has been a bit of a jerk lately.
You've been looking good for a little junior girl.
She's even prettier than usual.
So she's starting to get a little shaggy.
I'd like you to keep it clean and smooth when you have lessons with just Equal Love.
I'd like you to keep your hair clean and smooth.
I'd like you to keep your hair nice and smooth during your lessons at Ikolab.
Which member does Ms. Yamamoto think has a particularly bad sleeping habit?
By the way, who do you think has a particularly bad sleeping habit?
Well, I guess it's okay because it's my day off.
Iori, for example.
Her short hair tends to stand out.
She has a little bit of a sleeping habit.
I think that's cute, too.
Sana-chan, Morohan Sana-chan...
washes and dries her bangs the moment she arrives.
That's great, right?
She's so smart. She's so neat and tidy.
She got herself ready in the lesson room.
Is everything all right, since you were clean in the end?
Yes. Thank you very much.
Now, let's start with an onomatopoeia for your producer
Rino Sasahara, your producer.
I would like to ask you to present your onomatopoeia for Rino Sasahara, your producer.
Let's start with Hitomi Takamatsu.Let's start with Hitomi Takamatsu.
Hitomi Takamatsu will give a sasamatopee presentation.
Ms. Takamatsu, please.
Yes, I'm sorry, but I have a Sasamatopee.
I'll go this way.
Right away, right away.
Sugugugugugugugu?
Maybe it's not onomatopoeia.
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
Right away, right away.
What's this about?
Sasahara-san... you reply to my messages
He gets back to me so fast!
I'm so thankful for that.
I'm so thankful for that!
You're so busy, but you reply so quickly!
I'm so glad you're back!
I often have to think about what to do when I get a read.
If you are slow in replying, I sometimes wonder if it was all right.
Sometimes I wonder if it's okay if I'm a little slow in replying.
But since you reply so quickly, I don't have to wait that long.
I am grateful that I don't have that time.
Do you feel pressured to reply quickly?
But if you keep it open all the time, you think you're looking at it.But if I keep it open all the time, when I'm looking at it...
I can't keep the message open long enough for you to read it.
That's why I close it before Sashiara reads it back.
I have to close the message before Sashiara reads it back.
It's a game of speed, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Next, let's have Ms. Shoko Takiwaki
Let's have Shoko Takiwaki present the Sashimatopee.
Ms. Takiwaki, please.
My sasimatopee is "Bakubaku".
My blood is trembling, what does this mean?
My heart is already racing.
My heart is racing and my arms and legs are trembling.
The other day, Sanattsun and Sashiara-san
I went out to dinner with you personally for the first time.
At that time, Mr. Sashiara was there after me.
I was so nervous that I thought I could hear my heartbeat.
I'm so nervous, and I'm nervous every time, so I'm very nervous.
It has been more than 6 years since you met her, but your nervousness still remains?
Yes, I am. Yesterday, you came to my lesson again, and I was still nervous just by passing in front of you.
I really admire him. I am still a little nervous.
Next, let's have Ms. Maika Sasaki present the Sashima Toppe.
Ms. Sasaki, please.
ten, ten, ten, ten
10, 10, you also wrote the illustration.Ten, ten, you also wrote illustrations.
What is this?
This is yakiniku.
Whenever Mr. Sasaki takes me out to eat with him,
I often take Mr. Sasaki out to dinner,
And he always cooks the meat for me.
And he would ask me to eat it.
And he makes it sound like I should eat it, so I appreciate the meat even more,
I appreciate it because it makes the meat taste even better.
I am grateful to Mr. Sasahara, who is a senior producer and a great friend of mine,
Isn't there a bit of pressure to have Mr. Sasahara, a senior producer, grill the meat for you?
At first, I thought we might have to do it ourselves,
But Mr. Sasahara seems to like girls who enjoy eating delicious food,
Whenever I would see her happy face and enjoy the delicious food, Mr. Sasahara would also look happy,
I feel that she loves me very much.
What kind of meat do you usually eat with Sashihara-san?
When I go out for dinner with Sashihara-san, I usually order omakase,
There are a lot of meats that I have never had before,
He also tells me that I can order additional dishes if I like them,
He also sometimes tells me what kind of meat I should eat,
Thank you very much. I said, "Thank you very much.
It's really a luxurious meal time.
Thank you very much.
Next, Sana Murohashi.
May I ask you a favor?May I ask you for a favor?
My arrangement,
I'm just being reasonable.
I'm being nondescript.
I don't mean that in a bad way,
I mean, not in a bad way.
I met with Ms. Tsuchiura yesterday,
After all, Mr. Tsuchiura used to be an idol,
And she is also a very famous celebrity,
She gives me a lot of really great advice,
But she is even prettier than that,
She is wearing the latest makeup and fashion,
At first, I would listen to her ha-ha-ha, but then I would start thinking about how beautiful her skin is,
But then I start to hear things like, "Your skin is so beautiful,
I thought her nails were pretty, and her top was cute,
I'm not giving advice.
She is such a wonderful woman.
Is that advice still there? Are you okay with that?
Yes, of course.
Of course it's still there,
But she is even cuter than that,
The shirt was cute yesterday, too.
What kind of shirt was it?
It was cute, wasn't it?
The shirt has a border,The shirt has a border,
It's a little loose-fitting,
I thought it might be a little expensive.
And she had a belly,
I think "Sayuri Natsuno is nice, too.
I think of her as a fan.
You're already looking at me like a fan.
That's right. Really.
I also watch YouTube,
I really am a fan.
He's cute.
She listens to advice.
The time you spend with the really cute Saibara-san is precious.
Please make sure to leave that advice as well.
Thank you very much.
This concludes the talk session.